<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>based ventures</title><link>https://based.ventures/</link><description>Recent content on based ventures</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© 2020 based ventures</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 20:38:26 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://based.ventures/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lien Finance: The Global Internet of Value Movement Will Require a Truly Decentralized Independent Dollar (iDOL)</title><link>https://based.ventures/post/lien_finance/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 20:38:26 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://based.ventures/post/lien_finance/</guid><description>Stablecoins and the Price Volatility Problem Cryptocurrencies typically experience high volatility due to the complexities in valuing them and their smaller market size as compared to traditional fiat currencies. Volatility makes them less suitable for applications, especially those involving financial products and services. Stablecoins are designed as solutions to minimize price volatility relative to other crypotocurrencies. Stablecoins are usually pegged to other currencies and can be easily redeemed for their respective collateral(s).</description></item><item><title>Portfolio</title><link>https://based.ventures/portfolio/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Aug 2020 00:42:00 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://based.ventures/portfolio/</guid><description> Akropolis Curve Jarvis Network Kava Lien SKALE Stafi Tellor</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://based.ventures/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://based.ventures/about/</guid><description>Based Ventures is a blockchain-focused investment firm that takes a unique approach to searching for undiscovered opportunities through extensive research. From helping to develop their cryptoeconomic systems to incentivizing community growth, we will be there alongside these projects. With our wide network in both the eastern and western parts of the world, we are confident of leveraging them to bridge and build strong communities and meaningful relationships.
Based Ventures是一家新加坡专注于区块链的投资公司，用独特的方法通过广泛并深入的研究来寻找尚未发现的机会。 从帮助项目提升代币经济模型到激励社区发展，我们将与这些项目并肩作战。 凭借我们在世界东、西方广泛的网络，我们有信心架起桥梁并建立强大的社区和有意义的联系。</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://based.ventures/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://based.ventures/contact/</guid><description>Twitter: @BasedVentures
Email: business[at]based.ventures
Others: LinkedIn | Crunchbase
Alternatively, you may contact us via the form below:
Name E-mail address Message Send (Powered by Un-static Forms)</description></item></channel></rss>